John Capozzi
DC Public Library, Special Collections
John Capozzi Papers
1978-2001
DC Public Library, Special Collections
2.5 linear feet; 5 boxes
125
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1: D.C. Statehood, 1989-2000
  - Media, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Press, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Financial, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Retrocession, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Peanuts, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Human Rights, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alaska, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Puerto Rico, 1990-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Background and Literature, January-August 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Background and Literature, September 1992-1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Background and Literature, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Commission Meetings, 1989-June 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Commission Meetings, July-August 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commission Meetings, September-December 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Commission Meetings, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Series 2: Barney Circle Freeway Fight, 1978-1997
  - Correspondence, 1991-July 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, August 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Citizens’ Letters, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Citizens’ Letters, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Citizens’ Letters, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Legal, 1992-January 1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Legal, March 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Background and Literature, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Background and Literature, 1987-1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Assessment, 34912 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Stadium, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Press, 1978-1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Passonneau, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Series 3: Barney Circle Neighborhood Watch, 1989-2001
  - Meetings, 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Orange Hat Patrol, 1991-2001 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Background and Literature, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Series 4: Campaign, 1992-1996
  - Campaign, 1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Series 5: D.C. Politics, 1993-1995
  - D.C. Politics, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Series 6: Pollution, 1994
  - Pollution, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Series 7: General Press, 1990-2000
  - Press: General, 1990-2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Series 8: General Correspondence, 1990-2000
  - Correspondence: General, 1992-1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Letterhead, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Letterhead, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Letterhead, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Series 9: Personal Ephemera, 1993-2000
  - Personal Ephemera, 1993-2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)